I would give away my hearing
Перепонки и ушные раковины
To stay in dad's hands
Поменяла бы на руки папины
Tell me how to live on scorched earth
Скажи как жить на поле выжженном
When our closest are speared
Когда на ножи нанизывают ближнего
When soldiers are buried as stray dogs
Когда хоронят солдата как дворнягу
When for truth one gets impaled
Когда за правду сажают на кол
When a best friend kicks down your do or
Когда дверь вдруг ногою вышиб
And now has the prefix 'ex'
Твой лучший друг - с приставкой бывший
When eyes are corroded with poison
Когда глаза разъедает ядом
When there is no point
Когда назад
In going back
Возвращаться не надо
Don't come back, you don't belong
Возвращаться не надо ты ничей
A home is where the creek flows
Дом там где течет ручей
And where you are welcomed
И где тебе рады
There is no point in going back
Возвращаться не надо
Don't come back, the entrance is closed
Возвращаться не надо входа нет
A home is where you meet the sunrise
Дом там где застал рассвет
And where you are welcomed
И где тебе рады
Father, you can see from there
Папа папочка тебе же видно там
How poor are getting poorer
Как тихо в тряпочку беднеет беднота
Bunkers are built as wolf lairs
Как роют бункеры как волчье логово
How bloggers are getting louder
Как руки рупором сложили блогеры
How they swear, led to execution block
Как кроют матом их, ведут на плаху их
How brother fights brother, rattled with fear
Как брат на брата, ох стучит от страха и
How mothers moan, the sick without hospitals
Как стонут матери, больные без больниц
How we "traitors", yell from overseas
Как мы предатели, орем из-за границ
The eyes destroyed with deadly poison
Глаза разъело смертельным ядом
Back, back...
Назад назад...
Don't come back
Возвращаться не надо
You don't belong
Возвращаться не надо ты ничей
A home is where the creek sings
Дом там где поет ручей
And where you bring joy
И где тебе рады
There is no point in going back
Возвращаться не надо
Don't come back, the entrance is closed
Возвращаться не надо входа нет
Home is where you meet the sunrise
Дом там где застал рассвет
And where you are welcome
И где тебе рады
In going back
Возвращаться не надо
You don't belong
Возвращаться не надо ты ничей
A home is where the creek flows
Дом там где течет ручей
And where you are welcomed
И где тебе рады
There is no point in going back
Возвращаться, возвращаться не надо
You don't belong
Ты ничей, ты ничей,